
const STORE = [
  {
    question: 'What part of the body do dogs sweat?',
    answer: [
      'They don’t sweat at all',
      'paws', 
      'mouth', 
      'armpit' ],
    correctAnswer : 'paws'
    
  },

  {
    question:'At what age is a puppy ready to be adopted?',
    answer: [
        '3 months',
        '8 weeks',
        '6 weeks',
        '2.5 months',
    ],
    correctAnswer : '8 weeks'

  },

{
    question: "What are the names of President Obama's dogs?",
    answer: [
      "Bo and Mo",
      "The Obamas only have one dog named Bo",
      "Maggie and Max",
      "Bo and Sunny",
    ],
    correctAnswer : "Bo and Sunny"

  },

   {
    question:"In the movie Air Bud, what was the dog's name and his breed?",
    answer: [
      "Bud, Labrador Retriever",
      "Buddy, Golden Retriever",
      "Bud, Golden Retriever"
    ],

    correctAnswer : "Bud, Labrador Retriever"

  },

   {
    question: "What are dogs most closely related to?",
    answer: [
      "wolves",
      "bears",
      "coyotes",
      "horses",
    ],

    correctAnswer : "wolves"

  },

   {
    question: "Which breed of dog is The Queen of England’s favorite?",
    answer: [
      "Pomeranian",
      "Labrador Retriever",
      "Corgi",
      "Poodle",
    ],

    correctAnswer : "Corgi"

  },

   {
    question: "What is the most popular breed of dog according to the American Kennel Club’s registrations?",
    answer: [
      "Retriever",
      "Beagle",
      "German Shephard",
      "Labrador",
    ],

    correctAnswer : "Retriever"

  },

   {
    question: "What breed is Scooby Doo?",
    answer: [
      "Dalmation",
      "German Shephard",
      "Great Dane",
      "English Mastiff",
    ],

    correctAnswer : "Great Dane"

  },

   {
    question: 'Where is the breed "Australian Shepherd" from?',
    answer: [
      "Japan",
      "Australia",
      "United States",
      "Canada",
    ],

    correctAnswer : "United States"

  },

   {
    question: "What is the largest breed?",
    answer: [
      "Great Dane",
      "Irish Wolfhound",
      "St. Bernard",
      "English Mastiff",
    ],

    correctAnswer : "Irish Wolfhound"

  }

];
